<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PowerScout</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">SplashActivity</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">403488565329-3ntbedqgir4npi0kgqmbumt4i758pvd9.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">
    Terms and Conditions for Power Scout App\n\n
    Welcome to Power Scout! These Terms and Conditions govern your use of the Power Scout mobile application (the "App").
    By downloading, accessing, or using the App, you agree to comply with these Terms. If you do not agree, please do not use the App.\n\n

    1. Use of the App\n
    The App is designed to help users track and optimize their energy consumption.\n
    You must be at least 13 years old to use the App.\n
    You agree to use the App for lawful purposes only.\n
    Unauthorized modification, distribution, or reverse-engineering of the App is prohibited.\n\n

    2. Data Collection and Privacy\n
    The App may collect energy usage data, device information, and user preferences to improve the service.\n
    Any personal data collected is subject to our Privacy Policy.\n
    We do not sell, trade, or misuse user data.\n\n

    3. Accuracy of Information\n
    The energy tracking insights provided by the App are based on available data and estimates.
    They should not be considered as absolute values.\n
    We are not responsible for any financial or energy-related decisions made based on the App’s data.\n\n

    4. Third-Party Services\n
    The App may include links or integration with third-party services or APIs.\n
    We are not responsible for the content or security of third-party services.\n\n

    5. Limitation of Liability\n
    The App is provided "as is" without warranties of any kind.\n
    We do not guarantee that the App will be error-free or continuously available.\n
    We are not responsible for any direct, indirect, or incidental damages resulting from the use of the App.\n\n

    6. Changes to the Terms\n
    We reserve the right to update these Terms at any time.\n
    Continued use of the App after updates constitutes acceptance of the revised Terms.\n\n

    7. Termination\n
    We may suspend or terminate your access to the App if you violate these Terms.\n
    You may stop using the App at any time.\n\n

    8. Contact Information\n
    For any questions or concerns regarding these Terms, contact us at [Your Email/Support Page].\n\n

    By using the Power Scout App, you agree to these Terms and Conditions.
</string>
    <string name="esp8266_url">http://192.168.62.24/getSensorData</string>




</resources>